I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Fishing Hole"
"Erica Blige Dead.
The Mystery Deepens!! Suicide or Murder?"
The experts conclude that from the
remaining evidence, it was a suicide...
"Erica Blige Dead.
The Mystery Deepens!! Suicide or Murder?"
But there's no apparent suicide motive
for the diva who's sold
over 20 million records...
There're rumors that the
politically outspoken Erica
was silenced by the FBI.
Hmm? Hey, Ryusuke!
Did you see the
President's condolence statement?
Boy, that Erica sure was incredible,
mourned by even the President himself.
Hmm?
"'Requiem for Erica' Worldwide Release-
A Passionate Farewell Song
by her lover, Malcolm"
"Live 13
'Ciel Bleu"'
So, how are things with Izumi-chan?
I haven't seen her since that day
during summer vacation.
What about Maho-chan?
I haven't seen her...
since that day either...
Hey! Koyuki!
I don't mind joining your band!
Oh...
Bet no one else wants to play with you,
seeing how completely
ostracized guys you are!
Can you play an instrument?
I'll be doing the vocals!
Anyway, I want to stand out
at the Cultural Festival
and be popular with chicks!
To that end, I don't even care if it means
getting on Hyodo's gang's bad side!
You sure are a gutsy fella in a way.
With my networking, I can
guarantee us an excellent bassist!
I'm really something!
That's 60,000 yen per person.
We can't pay that much...
Oh boy...
Fine, I'll give you kids
a student discount.
Anyway, recordings do cost money...
But by selling our CDs at performances,
Beck receives greater exposure.
Let's go for it!
We have to strike while the iron's hot.
Yeah! I think I'm on fire!
Well, I guess I'm off to work.
Chiba-kun, what are you doing now?
Hmm? Working on a new drug.
I'll be back in about a week.
Yeah! Alright!
Wishing upon a star
We are apparition beasts
We fight for justice
And someday we'll be reborn
"We want to become human!"
Blast away our dark destinies
"Bem! Bella! Bello!"
Apparition beasts
Ta-dah! The name of the band shall be...
Ciel Bleu.
"Ciel Bleu (French)
'Blue Sky"'
Sounds like some kind of candy.
"Ciel Bleu (French)
'Blue Sky"'
It's "blue sky" in French.
Don't you think the chicks will dig it?
Well, yeah...I guess...
Let's wrap this up already.
Uh-huh.
Look over there!
What's a bunch of trash
like you doing here?
You really tick me off.
I'm a fan of your father's band.
Don't you talk about my father!
My mom's got all their CDs...
So I listened to them.
Mother and son, two generations of fans.
Let's go.
You sure?
Hey, wait up!
Saku, are you alright?
Yeah, I'm okay. It didn't hurt at all.
Well, when you go
back to school tomorrow,
your textbooks and notes will
be incinerated by those guys.
Huh? Yeah, but I just don't think
that Hyodo is such a rotten guy
underneath it all.
What?! But why? Are you serious?
I agree with him too.
You idiot!
You're the one suffering the most!
Is this some kind of bizarre empathy?
It's true; he can get under your skin...
He can really push your buttons, but...
I love his guitar.
Hey, is that you, Tanabe?
Eh, Esumi-san!
Are you on your way home
from band practice?
Yup, um...we're going to...
present you with a song!
Wow, that's so cool!
I'll be cheering from the front-row seat!
So cute...
Alright! I'm on a roll!
We'll be back in the studio tomorrow!
Yeah, you're right.
If we're going to do it,
we've got to do our best!
Umm, Sherry...What are we called again?
Ciel Bleu! It's the Blue Sky!
It's our youth! Esumi-san!
"Higashi Middle Festival-
Uplifting Power of Youth"
Please vote for the
Higashi Middle contest...
"Higashi Middle Festival-
Uplifting Power of Youth"
I'm going to be in it too!
Welcome to our haunted house...
"Yakisoba [Fried Noodles]"
"Yakisoba 180 yen"
-Um, can I get one order of yakisoba?
-Yep!
"Yakisoba [Fried Noodles]"
"Yakisoba 180 yen"
Hey, don't be eating there.
Hey, Koyuki!
Are you okay?
So, when are you on?
Pretty soon...We'll be rehearsing.
Hey, where's Chiba-kun?
He ran off to the bathroom.
I guess he got food poisoning from that.
"Candied Apples"
There. Thank you.
Darn it, that Saku...
Huh?
Hey, it's been a while.
Yeah, you're looking well.
You're right. It's rotten.
Saku, we're going soon.
Uh-huh.
I've had enough of you, you extortionist!
Extortion? What the?
Hmm?
I can't find my Dying Breed t-shirt...
Me neither.
This is awful!
I can't find my t-shirt!
Ours are gone, too.
-What shall we do?
-This must be Hyodo's doing.
Koyuki!
Come here!
This is terrible...
I begged my mom to buy that shirt for me.
My, what are you guys doing there?
What are we going to do, Koyuki?
It's alright.
We'll perform wearing our gym clothes.
Chiba's been in the crapper
for quite a while...
Let's see...Ah! We're last on the list!
We're after Hyodo's group.
The bands are listed in alphabetical order
by the band's representative.
Oh boy...They're great.
They aren't at a school level.
Yeah...
These boys sure are good!
So sweet, I kill you
So sweet, I kill them all, kill them all
So sweet...
-Hmm...He's good, that's true,
-So sweet...
but although his technique is good,
that guitar lacks feeling.
-But although his technique is good,
-I kill them all.
Yeah!
Eddy taught me this...
The guitar is a personality,
coming out of six strings...
What's important is the personality
that comes across
on the six strings of a guitar...
Performing last is the band, Ciel Bleu!
Hey, don't come out!
No one wants to hear you play!
Go back, Tanaka!
Stop playing!
Don't come out!
Huh!? Uh...
I'm sorry...I can't go on.
You handle the rest.
Ah! Tanabe!
What are we going to do, Saku?
The show must go on.
Uh-huh.
-Go home! Go home!
-Yeah, get out of here!
Everyone, settle down!
-It's no use.
-We don't wanna hear you!
Damn!
Shut up!
-Hmm?
-What?
Listen up!
This is the first and last time
you're going to hear Koyuki sing
in a shoddy gymnasium like this!
Hmm...
Well said.
It's the truth.
Living in the darkness, hiding
We are apparition beasts
-Koyuki's guitar's gotten pretty good.
-We are apparition beasts
-Yeah, he's been playing in Beck.
-Wow, Tanaka can sing and play the guitar!
-Unable to show ourselves
-Yeah, he's been playing in Beck.
-Wow, Tanaka can sing and play the guitar!
-Not these bestial bodies
-Isn't Tanaka-kun awesome?
-He's so cool!
-"We want to become human!"
Blast away our dark destinies
"Bem! Bella! Bello!"
Apparition beasts
Wishing upon a star
We are apparition beasts
We fight for justice
And someday we'll be reborn
"We want to become human!"
Blast away our dark destinies
"Bem! Bella! Bello!"
Apparition beasts
-Yo, Masaru...
-Ah...
Thank you for your patience.
I will now announce the results.
Hey, is it going to be Tanaka?
It's Hyodo!
I liked Kiss-Kiss-Kiss!
This year's Higashi Middle School Festival,
Battle of the Bands winner is...
Ciel Bleu, Blue Sky!
Hey, how come Tanabe's up there?
Saku!
Doesn't that look like the Grammy award?
Tanaka-kun!
Hey, Koyuki.
Chiba wants to see you at
the back of the school building.
Huh? But why?
Next, we will announce the winner
of the best guitar award...
This year's best guitar award goes to...
What's up, Rikiya-kun?
You stupid idiot!
Hey, Masaru! When did I ask to
get reimbursed for that guitar?
Huh? What's this?
He apologized to the owner and
that guitar incident is over already!
100,000 yen for reimbursement?
How dare you use my name like that!
I'm sorry.
Help...
Taking advantage...
I hate that kind of thing!
Hey, that's enough. Stop it.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me...
Damn!
Hey, kid.
Sorry 'bout that.
Ah...no...
I'll make sure that Masaru pays you
back the entire 50,000 yen you paid.
I-I'm sorry!
I'm...sorry...
Damn, you're despicable!
"Higashi Middle School Festival"
What's with that trophy?
It's the award for the Best Guitarist.
Well, I'll leave it here for you.
This one's broken, so I'll take it.
Momoko-sensei said she'll be
getting the other one next week.
Even though the results showed a tie,
I still think you're a better player.
Of course!
I got some bandages for you.
But you managed to get
this good in just one year.
In my opinion, you're the
first worthy rival I've met.
Pretty dismal isn't it, that trophy?
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Wow, the way the sound of the horns
reverberates throughout...
Gotta love it-Chinatown.